Fahmi Ichwanurrohman

Hardworking ... Passionate about Web Development ... Eager to Learn Magetan. Jawa Timur Phone number: +62 823-3433-7393

Email : fahmiiwan86@gmail.com

LinkedIn : https://www.linkedin.com/in/fahmi-i40a864111/

Github : https://github.com/fahmihwan
Portfolio : https://fahmihwan.netlify.app

Profile

As a full-stack programmer, I have 1 year experience in hospital to developing ERP - SIMRS, I can creating and managing database structures, writing complex queries, and optimizing SQL database performance. In addition to my technical experience, I have also been as a teaching assistant lecturer and training user. I am passionate about continuous learning and growth in the technology field. I am prepared to embrace new challenges and contribute to the success of the team and organization.

Experiences

PT.Subaga Digital Medika

Aug 2023 – Juli 2024

Fullstack Web Deveoper

With experience in the hospital, I've served as a Fullstack Developer, ensuring the successful implementation and operation of SIMRS applications. My responsibilities include:

- Understanding the hospital workflow, Training users.
- Customization features, fixing bug & optimization.
- Integrating with E-Klaim BPJS API, Bridging medical devices
- Working with Laravel, Angular, and PostgreSQL, Linux.

PT.Sinergi Digital Solusindo

Jun 2022 – Jun 2022

WMS Application Go-Live Trainer (Freelance)

When I was a bachelor's student, I took a job as a freelance trainer for one week at PT. Pertamina Lubricants, based on DSP Batakan, Balikpapan. My daily job was to:

- Train employees to use the Warehouse Management System Applications
- Working with their company to handle inbound and outbound
- Reporting issues in WMS applications to customer service

Alterra Academy

Feb 2022 – May 2022

React JS Front-End Engineer (Internship)

I also participated in a Study independent Program at Kampus Merdeka. I asked many questions and learned about web development. My daily tasks included:

- Learn basic UI/UX with Figma, Git, React.Js, Redux, GraphQL, and Deployment Project
- Making some mini projects
- Finished the daily task

PT.Gama Integra Informatika

Frontend Web Developer (Internship)

- Slicing from the UI/UX design wireframe
- Consume Api From Backend
- Build the Tambak Udang frontend using the Angular framework
- Collaborate with the System Analyst, UI/UX designer, and Backend
- mentoring class with materials about Analyst System, Ui/UX, Github, CI/CD, Angular, and Lumen JWT

Universitas Teknologi Yogyakarta

Sep 2021 – Jan 2022

Assistant Lecturer

- Teaching a web programming practice course for one semester (3 SKS)
- preparing learning materials about HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, ¡Query, and MySQL
- Create a weekly task
- Correcting weekly student tasks
- Creating student task assessment reports

SEVEN INC JOGJA Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

Web Programmer (Intership)

- Working with Ci4
- Fixing bugs at Djuragan.com

Skills

Laravel, Codelgniter, Express, React JS, Redux, Angular, JavaScript, PHP, Java, MySql, PostgreSql, CSS, Nginx, Linux.

Education

Universitas Teknologi Yogyakarta (Sep 2018 - Oct 2022)

Bachelor's Degree in Information System – GPA 3.26

Certifications

- Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Back-End untuk Pemula (Dicoding)
- Belajar Fundamental Front-End Web Development (Dicoding)
- Microsoft Office Specialist: Word 2016 (Microsoft)

Sep 2021 – Jan 2022